Fremont Rider Autograph Collection
Fremont Rider Autograph Collection
- Autographs
  - Phelps, William Lyon, March 30, 1937; author; professor of English, Yale University (Box 2)
  - Platt, Orville Hitchcock, February 25, 1885; U.S. Senator (Box 2)
  - Politzer, Irving, January 19, 1928 (Box 2)
  - Price, Carl Fowler, November 15, 1939; author of "Who's Who in American Methodism" among other works (Box 2)
  - Pulsifer, William E., August 29, 1916; D. C. Heath & Co. (Box 2)
  - Putnam, George Haven, June 8, 1922; G. P. Putnam's Sons (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Herbert, April 19, 1922; Librarian, Library of Congress (Box 2)
  - Raymond, B. P., April 23, 1894; President, Wesleyan University (Box 2)
  - Rice, William North, undated; American geologist, educator, Methodist minister and theologian (Box 2)
  - Richey, Lawrence, May 13, 1932; Secretary to President Herbert Hoover (Box 2)
  - Rideout, Henry Milner, June 29, 1925; novelist, editor, short-story writer (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Owen J., June 26, 1946; Associate Justice, U.S. Supreme Court (Box 2)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, May 27, 1946; wife of President Franklin D. Roosevelt (Box 2)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, March 1, 1922; U.S. President (Box 2)
  - Russell, Charles Edward, March 15 [no year]; Pulitzer prize-winning journalist, politician (Box 2)
  - Sargent, Porter, May 15, 1924; educational adviser, consultant (Box 2)
  - Sarnoff, David, May 20, 1946; Russian-American businessman, president of RCA (Box 2)
  - Sayles, Robert W., November 8, 1926; January 5, 1932; geologist, Dept. of Geology and Geography, Harvard University; curator, University Museum, Cambridge (Box 2)
  - Scaife, Roger Livingston, November 23, 1910; June 29, 1923; author; Houghton Mifflin Co. (Box 2)
  - Searle, Nancy, July 6, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Shanklin, William Arnold, December 18, 1911; President, Wesleyan University (Box 2)
  - Shaw, Mary, July 14 [no year]; American suffragette, feminist, playwright, actress [?] (Box 2)
  - Shearer, Augustus H., April 17, 1933; Librarian, Grosvenor Library (Box 2)
  - Sheppard, Morris, June 12, 1909; U.S. Representative (Box 2)
  - Sherman, Clarence E., November 18, 1936; Providence Public Library (Box 2)
  - Shipman, Herbert, November 4, 1912; October 23, 1912;; November 22, 1915;; May 26, 1916; Rector, Church of the Heavenly Rest, New York NY (Box 2)
  - Shotwell, James Thomson, May 21, 1946; Director, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (Box 2)
  - Sinclair, Upton, July 10, 1908; Pulitzer prize-winning author (Box 2)
  - Sirovich, William I., March 7, 1932; U.S. Representative (Box 2)
  - Smith, Alfred Emanuel, April 27, 1932; Governor of New York, Democratic presidential candidate (Box 2)
  - Smith, George Otis, March 8, 1922; May 8, 1926; Director, Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey (Box 2)
  - Snow, Charles Wilbert, June 14, 1932; Governor of Connecticut (Box 2)
  - Sohon, Julian A., November 4, 1939; Librarian, Bridgeport Public Library (Box 2)
  - Sokolsky, George Ephraim, August 19, 1946; radio broadcaster, journalist (Box 2)
  - Spellman, Francis Joseph, August 8, 1945; Cardinal, Archbishop of New York (Box 2)
  - Speyer, Edgar, November 19, 1924; financier, philanthropist (Box 2)
  - Stettinius, Edward Reilly, May 27, 1946; U.S. Secretary of State (Box 2)
  - Stewart, Lavinia, April 25, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, April 9, 1919; merchant, banker, publicist, philanthropist; Yale University (Box 2)
  - Stokes, Frederick A., May 17, 1912; February 14, 1918; publisher, Frederick A. Stokes Co. (Box 2)
  - Stout, Rex Todhunter, May 26, 1946; author, Nero Wolfe series (Box 2)
  - Stringer, Arthur John Arbuthnott, July 20, 1908; Canadian film writer (Box 2)
  - Taft, Robert Alphonso, May 28, 1946; U.S. Senator (Box 3)
  - Taft, William Howard, March 4, 1911; U.S. President (Box 3)
  - Taliaferro, Anne, May 22, 1906 (Box 3)
  - Tarkington, Booth, July 3, 1909; Pulitzer prize-winning novelist (Box 3)
  - Tassin, Algernon, October 15, 1912; professor of English, Columbia University (Box 3)
  - Tchernavina, Tatia, November 27, 1916; undated; Russian emigre, author of Escape from the Soviets (Box 3)
  - Thomas, Percy H., October 6, 1915; electrical engineer (Box 3)
  - Tien Hung-Tu, November 5, 1934; Librarian, Yenching University (Box 3)
  - Tolstoy, Alexandra, October 7, 1935; March 12, 1936; Russian countess (Box 3)
  - Towne, Charles Hanson, January 20, 1935; May 1, 1908; author, poet, editor (Box 3)
  - Trites, W. B., November 15, 1913; author, self-publisher (Box 3)
  - Tweedy, Henry H., October 31, 1934; Yale Divinity School (Box 3)
  - Urner, Mabel Herbert, January 18 [no year]; author of "Journal of a Neglected Wife" (1909) (Box 3)
  - Vanderbilt, Arthur T., November 11, 1938; Chief Justice, New Jersey Supreme Court (Box 3)
  - Van Hoesen, Henry B., January 7, 1941; Librarian, Brown University (Box 3)
  - Viereck, George Sylvester, September 12, 1908; German-American poet, writer, propagandist (Box 3)
  - Villiers, Alan John, January 6, 1937; January 11, 1937; author, adventurer, photographer, Master Mariner (Box 3)
  - Waldron, W. H., December 6, 1918; Colonel, General Staff, France (Box 3)
  - Wales, Hubert, October 3, 1908; January 18, 1909; author, novelist (Box 3)
  - Wall, Alexander J., January 24, 1923; Librarian, New York Historical Society (Box 3)
  - Walter, Frank K., November 16, 1936; Librarian, University of Minnesota (Box 3)
  - Ward, William Hayes, September 22, 1910; Editor, The Independent (Box 3)
  - Webb, Sidney James, March 14, 1913; British socialist, economist, reformer (Box 3)
  - Weeks, Frank B., March 6, 1911; May 8, 1911; Governor of Connecticut (Box 3)
  - Welch, Herbert, January 29 [no year]; Bishop, Methodist Church (Box 3)
  - Welles, Sumner, May 23, 1946; foreign policy advisor, diplomat (Box 3)
  - Wells, Catherine (Mrs. H. G.), December 4 [no year]; second wife of author H. G. Wells (Box 3)
  - White, Stewart Edward, June 27, 1909; author of adventure and travel books (Box 3)
  - White, Trumbull, December 18, 1907; September 17, 1908;; June 22, 1926; author; first editor of Redbook (Box 3)
  - Wickersham, George Woodward, September 1, 1924; International Near East Association (Box 3)
  - Wilcox, Cornelis Dewitt, December 16, 1919; March 17, 1921; military author (Box 3)
  - Wiley, Louis, September 15, 1928; business manager, New York Times (Box 3)
  - Wiley, Harvey Washington, February 11, 1928; chemist; proponent of the Pure Food and Drug Act (1906), first commissioner of the Food and Drug Administration (Box 3)
  - Will, Grinton I., January 28, 1938; Librarian, Yonkers Public Library (Box 3)
  - Williams, J., April 20, 1881; Bishop of Connecticut (Box 3)
  - Williamson, C. C., December 8, 1932; February 11, 1933;; June 17, 1936;; November 20, 1936; Dean, School of Library Service, Columbia University (Box 3)
  - Willoughby, Harold R., January 19, 1940; January 30, 1940; professor, theologian; University of Chicago (Box 3)
  - Wilson, Carroll A., May 6, 1937; March 27, 1939;; March 29, 1937; author, bibliographer (Box 3)
  - Wilson, Francis, March 19, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Wilson, Halsey William, June 17, 1916; March 18, 1919;; March 1, 1934;; October 8, 1940; H. W. Wilson Co. (Box 3)
  - Wilson, Rufus Rockwell, September 21, 1908; The Malden Herald (Box 3)
  - Winchester, C. T., August 6, 1896 (Box 3)
  - Windsor, Phineas Lawrence, December 16, 1910; Librarian, University of Illinois (Box 3)
  - Woodhouse, Chase Going, October 4, 1950; U.S. Representative (Box 3)
  - Woods, Elliott, February 7, 1923; Architect of the Capitol (Box 3)
  - Woolley, Mary Emma, June 15, 1946; educator, activist for peace and women's suffrage (Box 3)
  - Wriston, Henry Merritt, April 2, 1937; President, Brown University (Box 3)
  - Wyer, James Ingersoll, April 3, 1925; October 9, 1926; Director, New York State Library (Box 3)
  - Young, Owen D., May 8, 1935; industrialist, lawyer, diplomat (Box 3)
- Index
  - Card index to all items, in small box